No living creature was hurt
during the production of this show.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Allah is eternal!
Where did they come from?
Allah is with us!
Allah is eternal!
Kill the infidel!
Allah is the greatest!
Malhun Hatun.
Kalanoz!
Soldiers!
Attack!
Allah is eternal!
Let's go.
Will it be effective?
I saw it with my own eyes, Savcı Bey.
It's worse than a disaster.
What about the tunnel?
Nicola's soldiers will be happy to have
a grave.
Take cover, it's about to explode.
Ignite!
What have I done? Ignite! Ignite!
Ignite, ignite, ignite!
Ignite, ignite!
Malhun Hatun.
Do not stop my Alps!
My Bey.
Malhun Hatun fights like a man,
Masha Allah (praise be).
Man or Hatun, doesn't matter Boran!
She's brave!
Attack!
Why didn't it explode Goktug?
He needs time to run away.
It must be about to explode.
I hope it does!
You're out, but Cerkutay?
Where is he?
He must have been out by now.
Ignite!
Let's go Savcı Bey, let's go.
Cerkutay!
Cerkutay! Brother!
Open your eyes brother!
Cerkutay!
Cerkutay! Open your eyes brother!
Cerkutay! Brother! Cerkutay!
Cerkutay!
Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
Brother open your eyes!
Brother!
His heart doesn't beat!
Cerkutay!
I listened to you heart!
You heart wasn't beating!
How can it be!
Allah created me upside down.
My heart is in the right.
Didn't I tell you that
Cerkutay wouldn't die?
Let's kill if anyone's left!
Go!
What's it, madgirl?
Your eyes are watery?
It's because of the dust after the
explosion.
Get up already! Are you going to
lay down or fight?
Let's go!
Let's go.
You killed my brother!
Your brother had what he deserved!
Now it's your turn!
Tunnels blew up sir.
- What do you mean blew up?
- Just blew up, sir.
- What the hell do you mean?
- All of our soldiers were there sir.
Tunnels became a grave for all of us.
We will retreat!
Retreat!
No infidel left alive.
- They're all dead.
- That was clean.
Cerkutay is dirty, though.
Maybe he gets a shower now.
I just had a shower. I was on a frozen
lake, I fell in the water.
That was a couple springs ago.
Bury the dead soldiers according to
their religion. Talk to Papa.
- Eyvallah my Bey.
- Let's help Osman Bey!
Let's go!
Retreat!
Retreat! Retreat!
Why are we retreating?
We could defeat them.
But Osman blew up the tunnels!
Thank Allah.
You saved my life Osman Bey.
The alps of two tents have merged.
We showed who we are to infidels!
May our partnerhip be forever!
May it be!
Game is over. Infidels drowned in
their blood.
They came to destroy Sogut, but we
made Sogut their grave!
We are keeping on, we yell victory to
break the enemy!
From now on, our way is victory,
our name is "The victorious"...
Until we make the religion Islam...
and the state Turkish!
Allah is the greatest!
Take the ashes of our dead soldiers.
Black Shaman Togay...
presents you the brave soldiers' souls.
Erlik Khan.
Accept it.
Nicola's soldiers were buried in
the tunnels.
- How can it be?
- It's the flying barrel.
I don't know how Osman found it.
From Nicola's castle, of course.
Osman took revenge for my soldiers.
Nicola's soldiers are dead.
After this lose,
he needs my soldiers more than ever,
Just like how soil needs rain.
Lord of Yarhisar has to keep paying taxes
to Seljuqs.
He knows his taxes he pay to Seljuqs
go to Geyhatu.
He trusts Nicola. He isn't strong enough
to disobey Khan of the Khans.
What are we going to do Togay?
We'll check if Nicola learned his lesson
when I sent him Commanders' heads.
If he didn't, we'll wake Nicola up
from his dreams.
Osman Bey is coming!
Long live Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Thank Allah, they returned with victory.
Thank Allah, my Gonca.
They are back safe and sound.
Hey Masha Allah, Hey
Masha Allah(praise be) sons!
What a victory!
What a huge victory this is!
You made the infidels regret it,
Osman Bey.!
- You are the man, you are the best!
- Eyvallah (thank you).
The righteous people always win,
Davut Bey.
Even if all the enemy attacks, they
can't dfefeat the righteous people.
You are right, Kumral Abdal, the only
thing enemy gets is defeat!
You're in the tent from now on,
you'll see many victories inshallah.
Thank you, thank you.
May your victory be everlasting,
Osman Bey.
Thank you my Bala.
Brother.
Thank you. We'll have many more victories
if Allah permits.
Inshallah (if Allah permits)
Inshallah my Bey.
We don't doubt, Osman Bey
May your holy war be blessed, my Bey.
Thanks to your prayers, Hatun.
Take a rest, you must be hungry.
I don't know, I must be hungry
I tihnk.
Excuse us. We shall go to our tent. We
will notify Umur Bey.
May Allah bless you Malhun Hatun.
You helped us a lot.
You paved the way for victory.
War is our thing, Osman Bey.
I owe you my life.
Do not even mention it.
You owe your life only to Allah.
Tell Umur Bey that I invite you.
I wait for him in my dinner.
Of course, Osman Bey. Umur Bey will
be pleased.
Eyvallah (thank you).
- My Ahmet Alp.
- May your victory be everlasting, Osman Bey.
Hey Mashallah(praise be), I'd die for you!
Here we go!
Come on Bala.
Can I come in Bamsı Bey?
Come in Cerkutay, come in!
My Bey, you stopped me once, but I
blew up Sogut this time.
Mad man, you were supposed to blew
up only the tunnels!
Even I nearly blew up myself, my Bey.
Cerkutay.
How is your hand my Bey?
Did the cure work?
Where did you find them?
Osman Bey commanded.
We got it from Melik's store.
Cerkutay, is these the betrayer
Idris' remedy?
- Yes, this is it.
- Are you serious Cerkutay?
My Bey, your hand will recover.
You'll be Bamsı the double weapon again!
Oh Cerkutay oh! So you're saying that
Bamsı Bey attend fights with double weapon!
Let's apply it, Cerkutay.
What happened Cerkutay?
Bamsı Bey.
You'll teach me how to use
double swords, right?
You promised.
Cerkutay, Cerkutay, Cerkutay,
once I heal up...
Once I heal up, I'll teach you everything!
My Bey, this is the first apply.
It worked, son.
I'm recovering.
I'll fight from now on.
Mashallah.
Oy Cerkutay oy.
Oy Bamsı Bey Oy.
- Mashallah, huh?
- Mashallah(praise be!) my Bey.
Mashallah, Mashallah.
It was a huge war.
You broke the infidels.
Mashallah.
However, Nicola knows we joined
Osman Bey in the war.
This is going to be rough.
He'll want to meet me.
We have to stop our trade
with Nicola, my Bey.
We don't have another option to
infiltrate in the castle. Not now Malhun.
Osman Bey is satisfied with our help,
I think.
He invites us to dinner.
So he wants to get closer.
He found the betrayer in his tent.
He'll be stronger now.
I saw him in the battlefield, father. He
was strong, he was wise.
He saved my life.
Okay, good.
Muslums take care of each other
in battlefield.
Excuse me then, my Bey.
Malhun.
So, what do you think of Osman Bey?
You were used to say he was our blood,
he was Ertugrul Ghazi's son...
before we land here.
You were right my Bey.
Only this?
Isn't this enough, father?
You can go.
Have rest, daughter.
Bahadır!
Yes my Bey.
Tell me what happened in the battlefield.
Osman Bey put us under his brother
Gündüz's order, my Bey.
We did our job.
Didn't Malhun say anything?
She didn't, my Bey.
She didn't ha?
She got under Gündüz Bey's order
by one word of Osman Bey, ha?
Because of you! Because of you!
Because of you!
I lost because of you!
Do you see it?
I prepared it for you.
I am begging you, sir.
I am innocent.
Whose fault is this if it not yours?
Whose fault is it?
Sir, I am innocent.
I held you responsible for everything!
You are the guilty one!
- It's your fault!
- I am begging you!
It's your fault!
I lost because of you!
I lost because of your silliness!
Because of your silliness!
Look!
Your grave is ready!
Who did it if it wasn't you?
- I am begging you sir.
- Tell me!
I was hiding it in my castle! How did you
lost it!
How did you lost it!
How can it be?
No, sir. I am begging you.
Please don't kill me.
How could you lost it!?
How could you?
- Where is it now?
- I don't know anything.
Please sir don't kill me.
Whose fault is this if it is not yours?
Who was responsible?
Sir, sir please. I am begging you sir.
- Osman.
- What Osman.
He shot Dündar with an arrow
and killed him.
It was Dündar!
Osman learned I killed potter Idris.
It was Dündar.
He saw the tunnels in the map...
when he came here.
So he told everything to Osman
before he died.
Osman..
Osman's friends are increasing...
...and his foes are diminishing.
Send a messenger to Umur Bey.
I want to see him in my castle.
-Get out!
-Right away, sir.
You will pay for helping Osman!
You will! You will!
You will pay!
My Allah, give us halal food,
a fate without hypocrisy...
...and faith without doubt.
-Amin.
Make the hearts of those who sit here
closer to those of the others.
-Amin.
And make this unity stand forever.
Did you get used to the tribe, Kumral
Abdal? Was Osman Bey right to invite you?
Our hearts were in the same place,
now so are we, my sheik.
Thank you.
Now, my sheik Edebali will illuminate
Söğüt with his light.
And Kumral Abdal's fire will burn
in our tribe.
Not at all.
Won't you miss the mountains,
the forests, Kumral Abdal?
Of course, Bala Hatun. I'll be on
the ways when I do.
We are grateful for being destined
with victory.
Osman Bey, may your sword always
be sharp.
Amin, my sheik. Amin.
But...
keep praying for us.
As you stand together against the
enemies of Islam...
Muslims will be secured from the
dangers of the heathens.
My sheik, don't worry.
We drew our swords against
the enemies of the faith.
But Osman as long as Osman Bey tells
his own commander to lead our alps...
this will make us feel humiliated.
Mashallah, they fought well.
Malhun Hatun made the victory
easier.
We did our job, Osman Bey.
-Nikola will seek revenge now.
-Right.
Right. But after the damage
he took...
it won't be an easy recovery.
We still need to be careful.
Togay is back.
Umur Bey, you should
be careful too.
You can never know where and when
that snake will attack.
Either night or morning...
whenever he comes,
wherever he comes from...
our alps stand ready
and eager to fight.
-Don't worry, Osman Bey.
-Mashallah. Mashallah.
Don't act on your own.
Tell us when something happens.
We would love to help our brothers.
We know, Osman Bey.
Whenever you need us, we are ready.
Thank you.
Villagers, merchants, shopkeepers...
they are all migrating to Osman's
tribe!
I should've paid the tax
to the Seljuks, Nikola!
Enough, Yasu.
-Have they all left?
-Some stay at Yarhisar.
But I'm sure that they are preparing
to leave.
I will kill them all and send their
corpses to Osman's tribe!
Now, listen to me well, Yasu.
You will make sure that they all
reach to Osman's tribe.
Then, you'll place your most
trusted man...
among them.
That man will bring you information
from Osman.
And you'll know where Osman is.
And you won't come to me and
cry like a child again, Yasu.
Now leave and do as I say.
-What is happening here?
-We are here to see Osman Bey.
-What's the situation?
-They want to see Osman Bey.
-What do you want from Osman Bey?
-His justice and mercy.
It is unbelievable! How can they take
refuge in Osman?
This is a calamity, Nikola!
If you lose your reputation, we'll
lose the war before it starts!
We need the refugees back before
Osman gets stronger.
Are you talking about
attacking the Kayı Tribe?
Yes! I'm talking about
uprooting that tree, Nikola!
How many soldiers do you have, Kalanos?
To uproot a tree...
you should be as strong as Hercules.
We'll get soldiers from the lords and be
as strong as Hercules!
Being like Hercules isn't enough
to beat Osman.
We need the god of war Mars
as well.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come!
Welcome.
Be at ease. I'm listening.
Go on.
My bey, we heard that you are
just. That's why we came.
-What's the problem?
-We ran away from the lord of Yarhisar.
The tax they gather for Seljuks and
Mongols is killing us.
Don't hand us over to them, Osman Bey.
Give us lands and we'll serve you
with loyalty.
Not at all.
Göktuğ, prepare tents for
our guests.
-Host our guests.
-As you say, my bey.
May God protect you, Osman Bey.
We knew that you would protect us.
Thank you.
Göktuğ, Boran.
-Provide every need they have.
-All right, my bey.
But keep your eyes on them.
There might be traitors among
those poor people.
Don't worry, my bey.
We'll be cautious.
All right.
Why don't we kill both of
them here?
We need Togay for the refugees,
Kalanos.
You will learn to be patient.
Did you think that you'll be free of
Geyhatu's wrath by taking my sword?
Get out. All of you.
Get out.
What if there is more to that, Osman Bey?
Maybe it's Nikola's plan.
While we were waiting for Nikola's next
move, this makes me think.
But you let them settle in our tribe.
If Nikola thinks of a new move...
we need to use that
for our advantage.
If we take our caution, then
we'll win.
And we'll beat the unity
of those lords.
Brother, think about it.
We are showing the justice and the
toleration of the Kayı.
We are destroying the crusader alliance!
Then, all the non-Muslims
who complain about their lords...
will take refuge in us.
We will turn this to our advantage.
But if we'll take them in, we'll
need more lands.
Then, we'll jihad even more!
We will, brother.
We will.
-Together!
-Thank you.
Do you know what I see when I look
at you, Nikola? A clumsy cat...
who likes fish but afraid to get into
the river.
And two-faced too.
Traitor. You betrayed me.
You dishonored your word.
Camuha...
who worked with Osman,
killed my soldiers.
So, we are even.
What else do you want, Togay?
If you are here, you'll suggest an
alliance against Osman.
I don't need an alliance against Osman.
You do.
He buried your dreams
in the tunnels.
Did you give him the
fire barrells...
to explode the tunnels?
You couldn't even protect your
fire barrels.
Firstly, look at your friends
that you trade with.
Togay, what do you want?
You and the lord of Yarhisar...
must've received your gifts.
-This is Yaso's coltan.
-Is this Osman's work?
It's Togay's.
You will convince the lords
to pay their taxes.
Otherwise, you know what happens.
The people of Yarhisar took refuge
in Osman, Togay.
-What does that mean?
-Farmers, merchants, shopkeepers...
everyone who pays taxes for Geyhatu
takes refuge in Osman.
So, there is no better time to
make an alliance.
Bring the refugees and take
the taxes.
Or...
Or we can do this.
You and I can fight.
Then, you can see if I'm a
clumsy cat...
or a bloody lion.
Only Osman can benefit from
our fight, Togay.
But if we unite for a final blow...
we both can benefit.
I will take the refugees from Osman.
And the lord of Yarhisar will pay taxes.
And Osman will die.
It's simple.
-Will we trust these barbarians?
-For now, Kalanos.
For now, we need each other.
What about later?
Will Nikola keep his word
after getting the refugees?
He will keep it as long as he needs our
warriors. We need his soldiers too.
Go to Osman. Ask for the refugees.
-What if he refuses?
-If he does...
he knows that I will be with
Nikola.
If he doesn't work with me,
he will pay for it.
You are our guests at our tribe until
we find you a place.
Feel like home.
Come to me if you need anything.
May God protect Osman Bey's
compassionate wife.
-I brought apples!
-Bring it.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy it.
Here it is.
You too.
It's hard to leave your home, alps.
They are poor. We need to make
them feel good.
They are sent to us by Allah.
Don't worry, Kumral Abdal.
We'll protect them.
We'll help them with Allah's help.
We won't separate them from the Muslims.
We'll show them the beauty of our
laws and our religion.
May Allah bless you.
May Allah bless us all, Kumral Abdal.
Come here, come here.
Come here.
Mashallah.
Come on now.
-Alps!
-May God protect you, Osman Bey.
Not at all. Not at all
May God protect you, Osman Bey.
You trusted our justice and gathered
under our flag.
Now, now you are in security.
Until you are given lands...
you are my responsibility.
We don't discriminate among the
people.
In my lands, the security of your
religion...
food and dignity is secured
by...
Ertuğrul Ghazi's son Osman Bey.
May God protect you Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Brother, let's go Söğüt.
Osman Bey. We have another guest.
I came here as the messenger
of the Ilkhaganete.
I'm unarmed.
I have things to say.
We searched him. He is clean.
Take him to my tent.
Inform Bamsı Bey.
-As you order, my bey.
Won't you get down from your
throne...
and welcome your friend...
Tekfur Nikola?
-What are you planning Umur Bey?
First, you came here and talked about
friendship then you gave your men to Osman.
Tell me, what are you planning?
What's this anger, Nikola?
Welcome me first.
What are you planning?
Somehow, Osman Bey took
my daughter...
Malhun's mind away.
Maybe he took his heart as well, Umur Bey.
She took her alps and went
to Osman without telling me.
I wouldn't allow it if I knew it.
Trust me, trade with you is more
important than anything.
Without trade, what's the point
of staying here?
From Kızılbeyoğulları, Umur...
Bey.
How will I know that you and
Osman aren't playing together?
If you had thought that...
you would've beheaded me.
How do you know that I won't
behead you now?
You need me as much as I need you...
Nikola. That's why we are allied.
Osman can offer you what I offer you...
Umur Bey.
-I want trade.
And trade comes from İnegöl...
İznik, Bursa and even Constantinople.
I want to grow.
Come on, Nikola.
Smile to your friend.
Osman Bey.
The last time I heard, you were slaughtering
the Byzantines running away from me.
What is it? Did Togay send you to
show goodness?
We heard that Tengry sent you unexpected
guests from Yarhisar, Osman Bey.
They took refuge in you.
They did it without asking us.
And you accepted them without
asking us.
You washed the whole world with
blood...
You even dare to step over Genghis Khan,
huh?
Didn't Genghis Khan said that Tengry's
unexpected guests can't be touched...
just as my ancestor Oghuz Khan said?
Tell me!
Did someone step on that Dark Shaman
Togay's tail?
Don't speak Genghis Khan's name,
Osman Bey!
Osman Bey.
Bamsı Bey, hold on.
I will remind Togay the words
of Genghis Khan.
''Don't touch Turks as long as
they don't touch you.''
If you target those who take
refuge in me...
I will take his eyes out...
before beheading him.
If you don't give us the refugees...
we'll raze your tribe, Osman Bey.
He knows that he can't beat me...
now he wants to tyrannize
those poor people.
What is it? Do you want to ally
Nikola who you have betrayed?
Are you after the gold that goes
to the Ilkhaganete treasury?
Tell me!
Kayı Tribe is a lion's den.
Weasels like you have no chance.
Just dare to come.
Then, we'll drown you in
your blood.
So, you want us to bad to attack you?
You will get what you want, Osman Bey.
Bamsı Bey.
You had things to say to Camuha.
I do, Osman Bey. I do.
I'll send my regards to Togay.
And I will tell him...
The revenge of Abdurrahman Ghazi
will be taken.
Now, take this weasel away.
We'll avenge Abdurrahman Ghazi,
Bamsı Bey. Don't you worry.
I know, Osman Bey.
Thank Allah.
My beys.
-Tell me what you think.
-It's about taxes, it seems.
Geyhatu is after the taxes.
We can stop Togay, of course.
But if Geyhatu himself comes...
No, Geyhatu is busy.
He can't come here among
all the trouble he has.
-He left it for Togay.
-Those who come won't leave alive.
They won't dare to attack when
the Kayı alps are here.
When did Muslims hand over their
refugees?
He'll do everything to get the taxes.
He'll even ally with Nikola.
If needed, he'll attack our tribe.
But we won't hand over our refugees.
And we won't bow down to this threat.
Brother, prepare for war.
-All right.
-It's time for Togay to learn...
what happens to those who
touch the Turks.
Osman won't give the refugees.
I failed to convince him.
He will. Either with his hands...
in peace as morning winds...
or without his will, with no mercy.
Ready my horse.
The donkey that carries us all the time...
is better than the horse that is ready
to kick us, Camuha.
Nikola will be happy to see us.
I'm sure of that.
Nikola seems convinced.
But we need to be more careful.
We need to be cautious about supporting
Osman Bey from open.
-What do you want us to do, father?
-For a while...
we shouldn't be seen around.
Otherwise, both our trade and our plans
for İnegöl will fail.
We'll stay back from jihad to infiltrate
İnegöl.
Isn't this the real jihad?
Isn't it the real jihad to get into the
enemy's heart and finishing it for good?
You know it better, father.
Something is off with you.
-What is it, father?
-You wouldn't question my orders before.
I wasn't doing my job well then.
My job isn't to undermine you.
Those who say yes to every order are the
ones who undermine you.
Do you know what I'm most proud of?
That I raised you to be like this.
My bey, the lords sent soldiers to Nikola.
Nikola is preparing for an attack
to get the refugees back.
We need to stop them from
supporting each other.
We can't stop them before crushing
the snake's head.
Call Süleyman and Melik.
What are you doing here?
Come on!
You will take this letter to the Pope.
So, you are releasing us, Osman Bey?
You know that I keep my words, Petros.
As much as I trust the Pope's words.
But...
there is one last job that I want
Melik to do.
What is it?
You will go to İnegöl.
You will find out how many soldiers
have the lords sent to Nikola.
And when they will attack.
-Then, this captivity will end, is that so?
-It will.
It will be your redemption.
What if Nikola find it out and kills me?
Then I will send your heads...
with this letter...
and send them to the Pope.
Now leave.
Simon, when the battle ends...
if your intelligence proves to be true...
then, my alps will take you to Cunda.
You will take a boat there.
-Boran. Take them to their tents.
-Yes, my bey.
As you order, my bey.
Did Osman accept the offer?
No.
I didn't expect anything else.
This is the time to unite our forces for
one last time with no treason.
I don't need the Byzantine armies...
for the sun to warm the earth.
In my absence, you rolled dices and lost.
Now you will obey my power.
If your victory will be mine,
you will listen to every word...
Togay the Dark Shaman speaks of.
Nikola will come with great numbers.
What about Togay?
Togay will support Nikola.
I mean, they will attack together.
-When will they attack?
-Two days later.
I want more information.
You will go to İnegöl and learn
everything you can learn.
You know that I keep my words.
Alps.
My beys.
You heard everything.
Now, tell me what you think.
We can beat both the heathen Nikola
and the heathen Togay.
Thank Allah.
But...
Osman Bey, we will have many martyrs.
We'll have many martyrs, Bamsı Bey.
But if the two armies come together...
the victory won't be easy at all.
We'll either set a trap,
divide them...
or we'll face an honorable death.
Savcı Bey talks about an honorable death.
Is this needed, Osman Bey?
Should we knowingly face death?
What else should we do?
Give up on our honor?
Should we give up on the future
of the Kayı, Davud Bey?
Will the Kayıs give up on their lives
to protect the refugees?
Losing our honor...
or losing our life, is that so?
Does a nation without honor
deserve to live? Tell me!
Who can live without laws?
Can they survive?
Even if my all sides get surrounded,
I will still fight.
Because I'm free.
As the battle gets greater,
so will the victory.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Now, the matter is closed.
Brother, prepare all the alps according
to what Melik said.
-We will fight.
-As you order, Osman Bey.
-Thank you, Osman Bey.
-Bamsı Bey.
Bamsı Bey.
How is your hand?
The cure. The cure works, Osman Bey.
It gets better every day.
I'll be on the frontline, Osman Bey.
Not now.
Not now, Bamsı Bey.
You are my castle.
The post of our tribe.
-I can't afford to lose you.
-Osman Bey...
I fought without this hand.
Why are you saying this now?
Camuha talks about attacking the tribe.
He might do mischief in our absence.
For this reason...
I will leave the tribe to you.
If it's the order of the bey...
I will follow, of course.
All right, Osman Bey.
Nikola.
A clever devil.
I won't survive that castle, Petros.
-Simon...
-I don't mind dying.
I'm ready to stake my life...
for you to leave this tribe alive.
But promise me, Petros.
Finish our mission.
Kill Osman.
May God be with you...
and vengeance be with me.
Bala.
Come here.
Come.
My sunlight.
Are you all right?
I am, Osman. What can trouble me
when you are here.
Thank you. What did you do?
Have you taken care of our guests?
We provided all their needs, my bey.
They are praying for you in their faiths.
May they live long.
It's important for them to feel good.
It's more important than anything
that the Kayı Tribe...
should become a home for all
the oppressed people.
The enemy wants them back.
They want to stop the oppressed from
taking refuge in you.
If we are a good host, we'll have
a lot more guests.
If they feel good, they will
stay here permanently.
If the Kayı Tribe will found a state
one day...
it will need a lots of people.
This is a turnout, Bala.
We won't give our guests to
the enemy.
Everyone will say that the Kayı
is the hope of the poor people.
And everyone will gather
under our flag.
Take care of the heathens, Osman Bey.
Leave the hosting to me.
Be at ease.
This belonged to my mother.
I understand. I understand.
I understand, Simon.
The tunnels collapsed and you couldn't
reach Helen. Is that so?
Yes. Everything happened so suddenly,
Nikola.
So, Simon. How did Osman hear
about the tunnels?
Dündar. He must've heard it
from Dündar.
So, why didn't we hear that Dündar
got captured.
Because Dündar got caught just
before the attack.
And I didn't have the chance to
inform you, Nikola.
I understand.
So, Simon....
forgive my curiosity.
One of those tunnels led to your
shop.
How did you not get caught?
Petros and I did everything
we can to convince Osman.
Of course, we aren't free of suspicion.
But Osman trusts us for now.
So, you convinced Osman, huh?
Yes. But Osman shouldn't
get away with it.
We should attack Osman without
waiting for a moment.
We should determine the time
and act accordingly, Nikola.
Of course, Simon.
Of course.
I will attack Osman's tribe suddenly
with the soldiers I get from the lords.
When?
Very soon.
But something in my mind...
Simon, I was thinking...
It must be hard to convince Osman.
What is it, Nikola?
Don't you trust us anymore?
Answer this.
I want to think that we still
are friends.
Of course, Simon.
Of course.
Dimos.
I saw him at the tribe.
There was someone else with him.
They were both captives
of Osman.
Who are you?
You are lying!
Nikola, you must believe me!
We aren't working for Osman!
Simon, where is Petros?
Have they captured him?
And they sent you to learn what
move will I make.
-Is that so?
-Nikola, we gave you many opportunities!
But you failed every time.
You slipped him away many times.
Now, do you want to make us
pay for your mistakes?
Simon, I'm asking for the last time.
Where is Petros.
I will tell him to come.
But if you act like this, you
won't get our support anymore.
What happened, Simon?
Have your holy pope, your God
left you?
What happened, Simon?
Tell me!
Go to hell, Nikola!
Every place free of the pope's
rats is a heaven for me.
Close it.
Now, listen to me well.
Return to the tribe.
Tell me everything that happens
in the tribe.
Understand?
Good.
Kalanos...
Osman knows that we'll attack.
He knows. He knows, Kalanos.
Osman is all alone.
He has no one else but his alps
in his tribe.
It's time to finish this.
If it's as you say, a battle between
Nikola and Osman is soon.
It will be as you say, my bey.
There will be a great battle between them.
Nikola wants the refugees and Osman Bey
refuses.
They will unite with Togay
and attack.
We'll be with Osman Bey in
this honorable cause.
No.
No? Will we leave a bey who fights
for his tribe's honor alone?
Bahadır.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I have to be seen like I'm in
peace with Nikola. That's my plan.
This isn't a game, father.
The Kayı tribe needs help.
If we don't help now, there might not
be a tribe left there.
Osman Bey will take care of himself.
We will play our own plans.
Osman Bey will take care of himself
against both...
Nikola and Togay, is that so?
Yes.
My decision is final.
Are you thinking about the Kayı Tribe?
I'm thinking about you, my bey.
Your reputation.
If you allow me.
Why am I mad at her?
I caused this.
Bayhoca.
My dear son.
I still carry your smell in my heart.
I still carry your voice
in my ears.
You left and you won't return, I know.
But I'm still waiting.
I see you in my dreams every night.
I get afraid to wake up.
I don't want to wake up.
Yesterday, you were in my dream again.
I hugged you tightly.
To not let you go again.
My dear son.
Lena.
Lena, what are you doing here?
I'm talking to our son, Savcı.
I'm watering his good soil.
Savcı, is this our son laying here?
You know that it is the body
that lays here.
The spirit is in heaven.
In heaven, of course.
He is waiting for us, right?
When the time comes, we'll go as well.
We'll be united.
We will hug our son.
When the time comes.
I ask Allah to take my life before yours.
Lena.
-What are you saying?
-I can't live without you.
Oh, my suffering angel.
Would I leave you before your wiping
your tears away?
Don't leave.
Don't leave, Savcı.
Don't leave me all alone.
I can't bear it.
We will raise Ertuğrul...
together.
He'll become a valiant
like his grandfather...
a Ghazi.
-Inshallah.
You endured many troubles
since...
you became the bey.
You were betrayed,
you've lost comrades.
You were wounded in your
valiant heart.
But you endured them all at your feet.
Your name became the hope
for the Turkish tribes...
who cry under the scourge
of tyranny.
Eyes are on you.
Our prayers are with you.
Now, Osman Bey, what do you want from us?
Some non-Muslims from Yarhisar...
took refuge in our tribe...
running away from their lords.
But the heathens dare to ask them back.
The Mongols and the Byzantines
came together.
They want to destroy the Kayı Tribe...
and destroy the hope of the Turks.
It's not that easy, Osman Bey.
We are ready for afterlife,
we drew our sword for jihad...
even if they set fire the whole world,
we can extinguish with our heart...
even if they collapse the blue sky down,
we can carry it with our spears.
But my concern isn't about victory.
Victory belongs to those who believe.
My concern is bearing the Mongol
and Byzantine alliance alone...
and giving many casualties.
I want to divide the heathens...
and destroy them separetely.
You came here at the right time
for the right reason, Osman Bey.
You set the foundation of your state
by protecting the refugees.
We won't leave you alone.
Now, listen.
İkizce? Why İkizce?
Corpses with no graves.
A feast for the crows.
And it will be joy for us.
When we attack from two sides,
it's the only place Osman can run to.
Osman Bey, this Melik
still hasn't returned.
-Maybe he took refuge in Nikola?
-He doesn't go against his master.
As long as we have Petros, he
won't try that.
And he would've done that before
if he meant to.
So, there is only one possibility.
Nikola knows that we keep
Melik as a captive.
And he killed him.
-How are the alps, brother?
-Their mood is up.
Don't worry. They all know
the importance.
They are ready to fight and die.
-Are they ready for victory?
-Thank Allah, no one doubts that.
Brother! My loyal and enduring brother!
You did everything I asked.
You were always with me.
-I give you my blessing. Give me yours.
-What are you saying, brother?
Of course, my blessing is yours.
After my uncle left,
we are three brothers.
We should be closer, we should talk.
Know each other's value.
My brother, of course we should.
We are each other's everything.
The time that Allah destine us to live...
should be spent like this, together.
Inshallah.
Let us survive this war,
return to the tribe.
We can talk about our victory
and chat here.
-My brother Savcı will be happy too.
-Inshallah.
-Brother.
-Simon?
-Get up, you lazy man!
Is that you?
You should call me Melik now.
I want you to die.
I'm dead.
Now it's your turn, Petros.
No! No!
Where are you, Simon?
Where are you? Where are you?
Tomorrow, it's the battle day.
It's the day to settle everything.
I'll behead Nikola with
my sword.
Don't worry, mother. We'll strike
the heathens and come back.
We are destined with jihad.
You should get used to it.
Everywhere was white, mother.
A bird flied away from my mouth.
It flied far away.
It was like it was flying away
from a cage, mother.
-It flew away.
-No!
No! No!
Mother, I couldn't go...
Jihad is an obligation for the muslims...
you can't just stay, can you?
It is an obligation, Lena.
It is the greatest of the obligations
for the ghazis.
I know, you will go.
I know, there is no other way.
But it weights my heart, Savcı.
When I return with victory,
it will ease.
Don't worry, Lena.
I won't leave you alone.
I will come bag for you
and my valiant.
I will bring you good news.
Is there better news than your return?
The post of my tent,
the sultan of my heart.
My beautiful wife who
waits in my tent.
The reason I return
from victories.
The star of my night.
My gem.
-Does my father know that you are coming?
-Sooner or later, our bey will hear.
We are afraid that it might
be a mistake.
The mistake is mine.
You are my alps.
When did you see an order of mine that
doesn't fit an alp?
In that case, my life
and blood is yours, don't you know?
Come on.
My alps! Say what you will now.
We'll get in war with Osman Bey now.
If you don't want, return.
But know that...
even if I'm alone, I will stand
with Osman Bey until my last breath!
Malhun Hatun, Osman Bey is coming
with his alps.
Now, I'm asking for the last time,
is there anyone who wants to return?
-What is it, Malhun Hatun?
-We heard that you are going for jihad.
We want to join you in your cause.
The fate of these land that you came
to, depends on this battle.
Your alps are eager for battle,
I see that.
But they are concerned
about their bey.
My alps are ready to fight in your cause
for Allah.
The honor of fighting alongside you
is on my tribe...
and my bey's fury is on me.
I sacrifice my life for this cause,
Osman Bey.
It's an honor to fight alongside you and
this valiant woman, Osman Bey.
Malhun Hatun's valiant alps...
know that these lands that you came after
running away from the Mongols...
is the last haven of the Turks.
We will strike the last and the strongest
blow...
all together, against
all the mischiefs...
of the unhonorable enemy!
In the path that our ancestors opened...
you will cause the foundation of
a great state...
with your lives, blood and
Allah's help.
We won't bow down to either Mongols
or the Byzantines!
Neither their armies nor their
twisted plans...
will stop our unity!
Bravery takes us to victory...
cowardice takes us to defeat!
The power that we need
is in...
the noble blood we carry
in our veins...
and in our faith.
Here, I see such an unbreakable
will...
men and women all together!
I thank my holy Allah!
But don't you ever forget!
Allah... Allah is with us!
Allahu Akbar!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com